{
    "subject": "resource/Lilya_4-ever",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Works_about_human_trafficking",
    "human_readable": "Lilya 4-ever is about human trafficking.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6594993472099304,
            "question": "What is the topic of Lilya 4-ever?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6314968466758728,
            "question": "What kind of illegal activity is Lilya 4-ever about?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5643453598022461,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of the kind of exploitation shown in Lilya 4-ever?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49384573101997375,
            "question": "What serious issue does Lilya 4-ever address?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4565875828266144,
            "question": "Does Lilya 4-ever deal with a real-world problem?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43769314885139465,
            "question": "How might Lilya 4-ever make viewers think differently about this issue?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3435979187488556,
            "question": "What kind of impact could a film like Lilya 4-ever have on society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24992965161800385,
            "question": "What are some ways people can help combat human trafficking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23806606233119965,
            "question": "Why is it important to raise awareness about issues like human trafficking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.013157522305846214,
            "question": "Do you think films can be powerful tools for social change?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lilya 4-ever is about human trafficking.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6424_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is it important to raise awareness about issues like human trafficking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6424_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some ways people can help combat human trafficking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6424_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of impact could a film like Lilya 4-ever have on society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6424_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6424_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided clearly state that \"Lilya 4-Ever\" sheds light on the issue of human trafficking, explores themes related to it, and aims to raise awareness about this important social issue. The information in the documents supports the triple, confirming that Lilya 4-ever is indeed about human trafficking."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents clearly states that \"Lilya 4-Ever\" addresses issues related to human trafficking, making the statement accurate."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}